他在那呢
There he is!
超人 超人 我们能问你几个问题吗
Superman! Superman! Can we ask you some questions?
- 我们要做播客 - 那好吧
- It's for our podcast. - Well, in that case...
你一共救过多少人？
How many people that you saved... have you saved?
- 我… - 算了
- I... - Never mind.
那个标记代表希望吗？
Does your thing really stand for hope?
对 是的
Yes. It does.
但是它看上去好像"S"
But it looks like an "S".
是的 它本意是 本意是要弯曲 像一条河
Yes, it's meant to. It's meant to wind, like a river.
它来了又走
It comes and goes.
我父…
My fa...
我认识的一个人曾经说过
A man I knew, used to say...
希望就像车钥匙
that hope is like a car keys.
很容易丢 但如果你用心去找
Easy to lose, but if you dig around...
它通常就在附近
...it's usually close by.
- 你跟河马搏斗过吗？- 这问题太蠢了
- Did you ever fight a hippo? - That's dumb!
但是河马是最危险的啊
But hippos are the most deadly!
你最喜欢地球的什么？
What is... What's the best thing about planet Earth?
你在干什么
What are you doing?
等等 不要 等等 等等 等等
Wait! No, wait! Wait! Wait!
求求你 求求你老兄 求求你
Please! Please, man! Please!
你想要我怎样？
What do you want from me?
恐惧
Fear.
它们能闻到
They could smell it.
怎么回事？
What the hell?
- 那是什么 - 一个侦察兵
- What was that? - A scout.
外太空来的？外星大军？
From space? Like an alien army?
阿尔弗雷德 你看到这个了吗
Alfred, are you seeing this?
看到了 符合其它目击事件的记录
I am. Matches the other sightings.
这种图案在卢瑟的笔记里到处都是
And that pattern is all over Luthor's notes.
把飞机准备好 我今晚就北上
Prep the jet. I'm going north tonight.
好 是时候了
Good. It's time, then.
这是因为他们知道他死了 对吗？
It's because they know he's dead, right?
超人 他走了
Superman. He's gone.
我们以后要指望谁？
Where does that leave us?
《正义联盟》
(克拉克·约瑟夫·肯特)
(抵押品 赎回权取消 房屋出售 归银行所有)
(他们回到自己的星球了吗)
(我努力了)
把枪放下 马上
Drop your guns now!
请等一下
Excuse me?
- 快走 快点 - 不要开枪
- Move it. Move! - Don't shoot!
蹲下
Get down.
让他们靠墙蹲成一排 安静点
Line them up along the wall. Keep them quiet.
你是谁
Who are you?
赫斯提亚套索会迫使你说实话
The lasso of Hestia compels you to reveal the truth.
现在 告诉我你是谁
Now, who are you?
我们是一个小型复古主义恐怖分子
We're a small group of reactionary terrorists.
我们知道 罪恶降临在了这个
We know that sinners brought
- 瘟疫肆虐 - 为什么要挟持人质
- on this plague of... - Why the hostages?
你来晚了 倒计时已经开始
You're too late. The countdown's already begun.
几分钟后 四个街区…
In a few minutes, 4 city blocks...
"砰"全世界都会看到
While the world watches.
安静 闭嘴
Shut up!
这是人类最后的希望
This is man's best hope.
和现代世界一起沉没吧
Down with the modern world.
回到黑暗的年代
Back to the Dark Ages.
以及神圣的恐惧带来的安全
And the safety of holy fear.
这本来可以快速解决的 但是…
This would've been over quickly, but...
不 不要
No! Don't!
怎么可能
I don't believe it.
- 你是什么 - 一个信徒
- What are you? - A believer.
我想求你们的帮助
I'm asking for your help.
我相信有一个陌生人 从海上来到这个村庄
I believe there's a stranger, comes to this village from the sea.
他在冬天 人们饥饿之时前来
He comes in the winter when the people are hungry...
带着鱼
and brings fish.
他在大潮期间过来
He comes on the king tide...
也就是昨晚
That was last night.
港口那边有冰山
Icebergs in the harbour.
四个月没有船入港了
Four months since the last ship got through.
这个陌生人…
Well, this stranger...
不是坐船来的
Doesn't come by ship.
有敌人要来了 很远的地方来的敌人
There are enemies coming, from far away.
我需要战士
I need warriors.
我准备组建一支联盟 来保护我们自己
I'm building an alliance, to defend ourselves.
听着 如果你能让我现在见到他
Look, I'll give you $25,000 to...
我就给你
talk to this man right now...
两万五千美元
outside.
我感觉不管怎么样 这钱最后他都得给我
告诉我那三个盒子是什么 我给你三万
Tell me what those 3 boxes are and I'll make it 30.
你应该滚了
You should get out.
你至少能告诉我亚特兰蒂斯在那吧
Can you at least point me to Atlantis?
亚瑟·库里
Arthur Curry.
也就是海洋守护神
Also known as the Protector of the Oceans.
海王
The Aquaman.
我听说你能和鱼说话
I hear you can talk to fish.
所以让我捋一捋
So let me get this straight...
你的做法是打扮成一个蝙蝠 一个真正的蝙蝠
You do it dressed like a bat? Like an actual bat?
20年来在哥谭都管用
It's worked for 20 years in Gotham.
就那个屎坑
Oh, that shithole.
开战的时候 我们会需要你的
The fight comes, we'll need you.
- 别抱太大希望 蝙蝠侠 - 为什么
- Don't count on it, Batman. - Why not?
因为我不喜欢你跑到这里来
Because I don't like you coming here...
打探我的事情 干涉我的生活
digging into my business, getting into my life.
亚特兰蒂斯的人告诉我 干这个
People from Atlantis tell me, "Do this."
现在你说 干那个
Now, you say, "Do that."
我想要一个人待着
I want to be left alone.
这就是为什么你在这个荒芜的地方帮助这些人
That why you help these people out here in the middle of nowhere?
因为你随时可以走开？
Because you can just leave?
我帮他们是因为没有别人帮
I help them because no one else does.
你想要保护他们 你就得和我一起干
You wanna protect them, you need to work with me.
孤身一人才最强
A strong man is strongest alone.
你听说过吗
You ever heard that?
根本没这句话 你把那句谚语说反了
That's not a saying. That's the opposite of what the saying is.
是 但不意味着我错了
Yep. Doesn't mean I'm wrong.
你听说过超人吧
You ever hear of Superman?
- 他在和我一起战斗时牺牲了 - 我就是这个意思
- He died fighting next to me. - My point exactly.
那三个盒子里是什么
What's in the 3 boxes?
是个古老的传说
It's ancient history.
人类融化了极地冰盖
Mankind's melting the polar ice caps...
毁灭了生态系统 所以他们活该？
Destroying the ecosystem, they got it coming?
嘿 我才不介意海平面升高
Hey, I don't mind if the ocean rise.
那沸腾的海洋呢？
How about if they boil?
打扮成个蝙蝠
Dressed like a bat.
你疯了吧 布鲁斯·韦恩
You're out of your mind, Bruce Wayne.
并不意味着我是错的
Doesn't mean I'm wrong.
所以 你说 你没法再联系上这个所谓的…
So, you say you have no way of reconnecting with this...
海王
Aquaman.
我在他的外套里放了一个追踪器
I put a tracking device in his coat...
可他没穿就走了
He left without it.
也许那就不是他的外套
It may, in fact, not have been his coat.
卢瑟笔记里的 那些方块
Those squares, from Luthor's notes...
我觉得它们应该是某种容器
I think they must be containers of some kind.
装什么的？
Of what?
我不知道 金钱 权利
I don't know. Money, power.
某种值得为此开战的东西
Something worth starting a war over.
好吧 我们在这个人这里还有点运气
Well, we had luck with one person...
队伍名单上的
on the team list.
巴里·艾伦 中心城的人
Barry Allen, of Central City.
他完全处于离线状态
He's completely off the grid.
住在空建筑里 我觉得
Squatting, I think.
经常突然性搬家
Moves suddenly and often.
- 消失状态 - 但他还会拜访他父亲
- Disappearing act? - But he does visit his father...
去监狱
...in prison.
- 因为他父亲谋杀了他的母亲 - 我的天
- For murdering his mother. - Jesus!
小巴里一直在保护他父亲的清白
Young Barry always protested his father's innocence...
但他当时只有九岁 没人听他的
But he was 9 and nobody listened to him.
我们在监狱有人吧
We have somebody at the prison?
有 我们会找到地址的
Oh, yeah. We'll find the address.
那 戴安娜呢
What about, Diana?
你有她的电话号码
Well, you have her number.
你可以打给她的
You could've called her.
要不要我立刻飞到巴黎 带上你的亲笔信
Perhaps I should fly to Paris with a handwritten note?
"你愿不愿意做布鲁斯的队友？"
"Will you be Bruce' teammate?"
"请选择 愿意或不愿意"
"Check: Yes or No"
我只对她的能力感兴趣
I'm only interested in her skill set.
- 你当然是了 - 能继续吗
- I'm sure you are. - Can we?
这位的面部识别有点困难
Well, facial recognition's a bit dodgy on this one.
不过还是得到了部分匹配
But it's got a partial match.
维克多·斯通
A Victor Stone.
智商超高 拿着橄榄球奖学金上了哥谭市立大学
Genius I.Q., football scholarship to GCU...
而且 已去世了
And deceased.
猜到了 童话和鬼故事
Figures. Fairy tales and ghost stories.
有点想念以前
One misses the days
当时我们最大的烦恼 不过是会爆炸的发条企鹅
when one's biggest concerns were exploding wind-up penguins?
简单的生活
The simple life.
我已经认不出这个世界了
I don't recognize this world.
我不用认出它
I don't have to recognize it.
我只需要拯救它
I just have to save it.
我来见亨利·艾伦
Here to see Henry Allen.
签名
Sign.
快点 行不行
Hurry it up, will you?
怎么了 有问题吗？
What, you got a problem?
不 没有问题
No. There's no problem.
没有就对了
Better not be.
你知道该怎么走
You know where to go.
你是必须戴眼镜…
Are those prescription...
还是就想看起来聪明点
Or you just trying to look brainy?
因为你在限制自己的能力 你一直在原地打转
Because you're holding yourself back. You're going in circles.
你做着三个没有前途的工作 现在这是第四个
You're working 3 dead-end jobs. Going on four.
你哪来的时间
Where do you even have the time?
我会挤时间的
I make the time.
这一切 就为了支付刑事司法的学位的学费？
And this is all to pay for a criminal justice degree, huh?
好吧 我真的不想再讨论这个了
Okay. I really don't want to talk about this again...
当时调查简直一塌糊涂
The investigation was botched.
把手给我
Give me your hand.
我要你认真听我说 巴里
I want you to listen to me, Barry...
因为我是认真的
Because I mean this.
我要你放弃这些
I want you to give all of that up.
我要你不要继续来见我了
And I want you to stop coming to see me.
我就是你生命中的累赘
I am a drag on your life.
请别再对我说这样的话
Please don't ever say that to me again.
求你
Please?
你可以成为你想成为的一切 你那么聪明
You can be whatever you wanna be. You're a brilliant man.
绝对是精英中的精英
Absolute best of the best.
我不能呆在这里
I can't sit here...
看着你在中城跑进跑出
and watch you run in place in Central City...
为了一个老家伙
for some old dude...
哪里都去不了的老家伙
who's not going anywhere.
- 爸爸 这不是真的 - 是时候了
- Dad...That's not true. - It's time.
- 这不是真的 - 放手吧 艾伦
- That's not true. - Let's go, Allen.
艾伦
Allen!
我要你开创自己的未来
I want you to make your own future.
不要活在过去 创造自己的未来
Living in the past... Make your own future.
开门
Open gate!
实验室归你了 霍华德
Lab's all yours, Howard.
十一点半 今晚挺早啊 塞拉斯
11:30. Early night for you, Silas.
对 挺早
Yes. Early.
我没机会告诉你…
I never got to say...
我对这一切的发生很抱歉
I'm very sorry about what happened.
维克多是个好小伙
Victor was a wonderful kid.
谢谢你
Thank you.
维克多
Victor.
维克多 你不能就呆在这里
Victor, you're not stuck up here.
你可以拥有人生 可以拥有比…
You can have a life. You can have more than...
- 如果你在这里胡思乱想… - 我在处理
- If you stay up here brooding... - I'm processing.
我可以访问到一切数据
I can access everything.
- 但我无法把信息整合起来 - 还不能
- But I can't put it all together. - Not yet.
但是如果你和我合作 如果我们有再造引擎…
But if you work with me, if we had the change engines...
所以你还对其他人做了对我做的事情
So you did to someone else. What you did to me.
不 母盒必须被藏起来
No. The box stays hidden.
如果你看到我们从那艘氪星船上学到了什么
If you could see what we're learning from the Kryptonian ship...
我认为再造引擎可以感应它的能量…
I think the change engine can integrate with its energy...
- 可以升级… - 有谁知道吗
- get it powered up... - Does anybody know?
什么
What?
实验室里 有谁知道我还活着吗
At the lab... Does anybody know I'm alive?
我…我…
I... I...
我觉得你还没准备好…
I didn't think you were ready for them to...
准备什么
For what?
让他们看到怪物吗？
For them to see the monster?
你不是怪物
You are not a monster.
真是奇怪 你竟然以为我在说自己
It's weird that you thought I meant me.
我所做的…
What I did...
那场事故中 我失去了你妈妈
I lost your mother in that accident.
我不能再…
I wasn't about to...
我不能再失去我的儿子
I couldn't bear to lose my son.
但你已失去了
But you did.
现在我脑子里有种我不会说的语言
I got a language in my head that I don't speak.
不是数字信号 而是外星的
It's not just digital... It's alien.
每一天 醒来 我都不一样
Everyday, I wake up, different...
在进化
Modified.
你怎么…
How do you...
昨晚我还做不到
Couldn't do that last night.
自从氪星人拜访之后
Ever since we got visitors from Krypton,
人们就在等待下一次外星入侵
people have been waiting for the next alien invasion.
现在我在想 如果我就是外星人
Now I got to wonder if I'm it?
- 今天有什么变化吗 - 没有 女王陛下
- Any changes today? - No, my Queen.
母盒已经苏醒
The Mother Box has awoken...
但还没有什么事情发生
Yet, nothing has happened.
母盒从远古开始 已经沉睡了几千年
It has slept for thousands of years, since the first age.
为什么现在突然苏醒了
Why did it wake at all?
亚马逊族 准备战斗
Amazons, on your mark!
荒原狼
Steppenwolf.
母亲…
Mother...
我流放了数千年 一直在寻找…
Millenia in exile... Searching.
今天 你终于让我回家了
At last, you call me home.
你不会喜欢你的欢迎仪式的
You will not like your welcome.
我想我会的
Oh, I think I will.
- 召集军团 - 封锁牢房
- Gather the legions. - Seal the cage!
快去
Go!
右翼
Flank right!
对
Yes...
跑吧
Run.
封锁大门
Seal the gates!
别停下
Keep it moving.
拿到了 走
Got it! Go!
尊贵的女王 为何要反抗？
Noble Queen, why do you fight?
统一之力完成后 你将会加入我的军团
After the Unity, you will join my Legion...
到时你会明白权力就是正义
and you will know the righteousness of power.
你会爱上我的
You will love me.
你们全部都会
You all will.
我们必须点燃古代的烽火
We have to light the ancient warning fire.
烽火有五千年没有燃起了
The fire has not burned for 5,000 years.
人类不会明白它的意思的
Men won't know what it means.
人类不会…
Men won't...
但是她会
But she will.
听我说 戴安娜
Listen to me, Diana.
你这个周末干嘛了 戴安娜
What did you do this weekend, Diana?
我？
Me?
没做什么特别有趣的事
Nothing very interesting.
你每次都这么说
That's all you ever tell us.
我能怎么说呢 我是个无趣的人
Whay can I say? I'm not that exciting.
亚马逊人的神殿
...Shrine of the Amazons...
巨大的烽火 就在我身后燃烧
an enormous bonfire burned right behind me...
让大家都百思不得其解
baffling absolutely everyone...
不管是当地人 还是政府官员
from locals, to government authorities alike.
- 烽火在几英里之外都可以看到… - 入侵
- The fire could be seen for miles on end... - Invasion.
当地新闻…
On the local scene...
这位清洁工的妻子信誓旦旦的说
This janitor's wife had some strong words...
是那些外星人
for the aliens she says,
偷走了她的丈夫
stole her man.
我家霍华德是个好人 是家里的支柱
My Howard is a good man. He's a provider.
那些外星人是要在他的(消音)插探测仪吗？
And these aliens are gonna (beep) probe him?
你要敢来湖景公寓
Come down to the Lakeview...
我他妈要把又粗又大的探测仪插到你的(消音)去
And I'll stick a (beep) probe up your alien (beep) ass, you...
我找到个小地方 餐馆旁边
I found a little place. By the diner.
挺适合我的
Suits me just fine.
你怎么不早说呢
I wish you'd said something.
不 我只是欠了点账而已
Oh, no. I got behind in the payments.
你知道银行的 欠一毛钱都会紧追不放
And you know the banks. Jump like a cougar if you miss by a dime.
那地方反正对我来说也太大了
Place was too big for me anyway.
空荡荡的房子里像个鬼魂一样游荡
Shuffling around like an old ghost.
你早说的话我可以找人帮你 或者…
Well, I might have been able to, talk to someone, or...
你的事情够多了
You had enough to deal with.
没必要让你为婆婆操心了
Don't need to add mother-in-law to the list.
- 虽然不是正式的… - 嘿 莲恩
- Not that I was ever... - Hey, Lane...
你的线人是谁 大学里那个激进主义者
Who is your source? The activist in that university...
听着 是我的线人
Look, it's my source.
他们要我写那个绑架案
I got tapped for the kidnapping story.
只不过就是一些学生游行 总之…
There were all those student protests. Anyway...
我觉得这是政治的事情 所以 你的线人是谁
I'm thinking it's political, so... Who's your guy?
我看看她接不接电话
Well let's see if she'll take your call.
原来是个女的
So, it's a she.
不是女的
It's not a she.
看来你得忙那个故事了
Sounds like you should be working that story.
我… 我还没准备好
I'm... I'm not ready yet.
我现在很开心 写点小猫美容的新闻
I'm perfectly happy, doing fluff pieces about kitten grooming.
调节一下
For a while...
回来了 还是有些困难的
It was hard coming back here at all.
好吧 我现在新闻都看不下去了
Well. I can hardly read the news anyway.
都太悲伤了
So much bitterness.
当然 我想都是因为他走了
'Course, I think it's all because he's gone.
不过估计母亲都这样
But I suppose a mother does.
但是也不是说你要报道的事情就少了
But it's not like there's any less that needs reporting.
克拉克保证过 你还会再拿一个普利策奖
And Clark promised me, you were gonna bring home another Pulitzer.
- 是吗 - 当然 他说过
- Oh, did he? - Oh, yes. He did.
他说你是他见过最饥渴的女人
He said you were the thirstiest young woman he'd ever met.
- 最饥饿 - 饥饿 对
- Hungriest. - Hungry. Yeah.
他说你…
He said you...
你的新闻嗅觉是比他的听觉还灵敏
could smell a story. Further away than he could hear.
好的故事 都是有原因的
Well stories, made sense.
这不只是谜题 这更是有关真相
It was more than just a puzzle. It was about the truth.
要看到驱动世界的引擎
It was about seeing the engine of the world...
趁它还在转
While it still ran.
维克多·斯通
Victor Stone...
已去世
Deceased.
就是它…
That one...
可以确定这就是让外星人发狂的东西了
Pretty sure that's what made the alien go crazy.
我会考虑在战衣上加点东西的
I'll see about weaving something to the suit.
得花一点时间
Won't be quick.
只要能给我点胜算就行
Anything to give me an edge.
要知道 我可花了几百万美元
You know, I paid millions of dollars...
来建造这栋大楼的安保系统
for this building's security.
对 看起来就很贵
Yeah. It looked expensive.
嗨
Hi.
新玩具吗
A new toy?
军队运输机 原型机
Prototype troop carrier.
我曾经认识一个男人 他肯定很想开这玩意
I once knew a man who would've loved to fly it.
对 我们需要的不仅仅是个飞行员
Yeah, well we're gonna need more than a pilot.
我觉得敌人要来了
I think there's an attack coming.
不是要来 布鲁斯
Not coming, Bruce.
是已经来了
It's already here.
他们称他为荒原狼
They called him Steppenwolf.
世界的终结者
The End of Worlds.
他为征服而生
He lived only to conquer.
数不清的人倒于他的屠刀之下
Millions fell before his blade...
而后又以其类魔之身重现
And rose again as his Parademons.
噩梦般的生物 以恐惧为食
Nightmare creatures, who feed on fear.
对 我可能遇到过一个 我们不太合得来
Yeah, I think I've met one. We didn't hit it off.
在哥谭吗
Here in Gotham?
他们到处都是
They're all over.
他们是在找他的什么盒子吗？
They're looking for his... Boxes?
- 母盒 - 母盒
- The Mother Boxes. - Mother Boxes?
我猜荒原狼拿走了你们守护的那个
I guess Steppenwolf took the one you people were guarding,
这样还剩两个
that leaves two more.
- 你挺厉害嘛 - 过奖
- I'm impressed. - Don't be.
我不知道里面是什么
I have no idea what's in them.
是武器吗？还是某种能量
A weapon? Some kind of power?
它们并非蕴含能量
They don't contain power.
它们就是能量本身
They are power.
从一个星球传运到另一个
Carried from planet to planet...
母盒合并之后就能形成统一之力
The Mother Boxes combined to form the Unity.
那种灾难性的能量不仅可以毁灭世界
An apocalyptic power that not only destroys worlds...
还能把世界打回最原始的空壳
...but transforms them into the primordial hell's gate...
跟荒原狼出生地一样
...of Steppenwolf's birthworld.
我们本该灭亡
We should have died...
但我们迸发出了自己的统一之力
But we formed our own Unity.
亚马逊人 亚特兰蒂斯人
Amazons, Atlanteans...
所有人类部落并肩作战
All the tribes of man fought side by side.
传奇战士
Warriors of legend.
来自其他世界的盟友
Allies from other worlds.
就连众神也齐心协力
Even the gods themselves all acted as one.
不惜献出生命将荒原狼击退
Laying down their lives to drive Steppenwolf away.
据说这让荒原狼恼羞成怒
Some say it drove him mad...
这是他第一次蒙受打败仗的耻辱
.. the disgrace of his first retreat.
他发誓我们的联盟会瓦解
He swore our alliance would crumble.
黑暗将再次笼罩地球
That darkness would cover the Earth...
而黑暗降临之时 他就会再回来
And that he would return when it did.
留下的
Left behind...
母盒母盒太过危险
The Mother Boxes were too dangerous
绝对不能放在一起
to be kept together.
其中之一托付给亚马逊人
One was entrusted to the Amazons.
一个交于亚特兰蒂斯人
One, to the Atlanteans.
都封存在安全的要塞里 重兵把守
Both sealed and guarded in secure strongholds.
人类之盒被秘密掩埋
The Box of Man was buried in secret.
以确保没有部落能用它的能量攻击其他部落
So that no tribe would be tempted to use its power over another.
巨大恐惧之后的和谐来之不易
Such harmony out of such horror.
那可真是一个英雄辈出的时代
It was truly an age of heroes.
我觉得我们不可能再找回从前的团队了
Something tells me we're not getting the band back together.
亚特兰蒂斯人被迫待在海底
The Atlanteans were forced under sea...
而亚马逊人 藏于孤岛永不离开
And the Amazons, to an island they can never leave.
我不会依靠人类部落
I wouldn't count on the tribes of men.
我们总觉得末日闹钟还有个小睡模式一样
We tend to act like the doomsday clock has a snooze button.
- 我们还剩多久… - 几天
- How long until we... - Days.
最多几天
At most.
荒原狼上次的错误就是袭击我们
Steppenwolf's mistake last time was attacking us.
他想在毁灭我们之前让地球俯首称臣
He wanted to make the Earth kneel before he destroyed us.
这次他的目的只是想夺取母盒
This time he'll just go after the Boxes.
我收到了我们一个新队员的地址
I got a location for one of our recruits.
- 巴里·艾伦 - 另一个呢
- Barry Allen. - What about the other one?
维克多·斯通
Victor Stone?
我希望你能把他找出来
I was hoping you would dig him up.
我们是在请陌生人拿自己的生命冒险
We're asking people we don't know to risk their lives.
我知道
I know.
事情就是这样
That's how this works.
巴里·艾伦
Barry Allen.
布鲁斯·韦恩
Bruce Wayne.
你这么说得好像是在解释
You say that like it explains...
为什么我家里来了个陌生人
why there's a total stranger in my place...
躲在黑漆漆的屋子里 坐在我第二喜欢的椅子上
sitting in the dark, in my second favorite chair.
跟我说说这个吧
Tell me about this.
这就是个长得和我一模一样
This is a person who looks exactly like me...
但是绝不是我的人
but who is definitely not me.
很帅气的犹太小伙儿
Very attractive Jewish boy.
我猜猜 这个人偷了你的怀表吗
Somebody who, I don't know, stole your pocketwatch?
或者铁路？
Or railroads?
我知道你有超能力
I know you have abilities.
我只是不清楚具体是什么
I just don't know what they are.
我的超能力包括…
My special skills include...
拉中提琴 设计网页 精通手语
Viola, web design, fluent in sign language...
大猩猩手语
gorilla sign language...
硅基石英纱织物
Silica-based quartz sand fabric,
耐磨 耐热
Abrasion resistant. Heat resistant.
是啊 是我参加冰舞比赛用的
Yeah, I do...Competitive ice dancing.
这是航天飞机返回大气层所需的阻燃材料
That's what they use on the space shuttle, to prevent it from burning up on re-entry.
我参加非常激烈的冰舞比赛
I do very competitive ice dancing.
不管你要找的是谁 绝对不是我…
Whoever you're looking for, it's not me...
你是蝙蝠侠
You're the Batman?
所以你的超能力就是快
So you're fast.
这么说似乎太笼统了点
That feels like an oversimplification.
我在组织一个队伍
I'm putting together a team.
将有超能力的人组建在一起
People with special abilities.
你看 我觉得敌人就要来了
You see, I believe enemies are coming.
别说了 我加入
Stop right there. I'm in.
你加入吗？
You are?
对 我需要 朋友
Yeah. I need... friends.
人类很复杂 他们需要很多关注点
People are difficult. They require a lot of focus.
他们的节奏我实在是没法理解…
They have like a rhythm that I haven't quite been able to...
就像"早午餐"
Like, Brunch?
比如说… 什么是早午餐
Like... What is Brunch?
你排队等一个小时
You wait in line for an hour...
拿到的明明就是午餐
for, essentially, lunch.
我是说… 我也搞不清
I mean, I don't know.
人们就是… 有点慢
People are... a little slow.
我尽量跟上
I'll try to keep up.
这个能送我吗
Can I keep this?
我可以进入另一层维度
It's like this layer of dimensional reality...
里面好像能操控时空
that seems to manipulate space-time.
我将其称之为速度力量
I call it the Speed Force.
它让我每天都消耗巨多卡路里
Causes me to burn tremendous amount of calories...
所以我就是个零食黑洞
So I am just a black hole of snacks.
我是个"零食洞"
I am a "snack hole."
这个特殊战斗小队有多少人
How many people are on this special fight team?
三个 加上你
Three. Including you.
三个？敌人是谁？
Three? Against what?
我在飞机上和你慢慢说
I'll tell you on the plane.
飞机？
Plane?
你的超能力是什么来着？
What are your superpowers again?
我有钱
I'm rich.
每次播放这段录像 电脑就抽风
The program always gets twitchy with this footage.
(戴安娜·普林斯)
(为什么你和布鲁斯·韦恩都在找我)
你知道我们是谁
You know who we are?
(我还知道你们的另一重身份)
你是维克多·斯通吗
Are you Victor Stone?
(曾经是)
我得和你谈谈
I need to speak to you.
(你正在和我谈)
不 面对面那种
No, face to face.
在这上面 我很传统
I'm old-fashioned that way.
(我凭什么相信你)
如果我打算伤害你 我在湖边就动手了
If I was going to attack you, I would've done it by the lake.
看起来你有约会了 普林斯女士
Looks like you have a date, Ms. Prince.
这里有个人很久没约会了
About time somebody here did.
面对面
Face to face.
我一直在追踪
I've been doing some tracking.
你想找的东西待在盲区里面
What you're looking for is sticking to the dead zones.
一旦它现身 能量泄漏
It gets in front of a camera, causes a surge.
- 我会让你知道的 - 那不够好
- I'll let you know. - That's not good enough.
不够好？
Not good enough?
对你而言
For you.
听着 我不认识你
Look, I don't know you...
我不知道你怎么得到这些馈赠的
And I don't know how you got these gifts.
馈赠？
Gifts?
你能做到的事没人可以做到
No one else can do what you do.
如果这是馈赠
No, if these are gifts...
为什么只有我付出代价
then why am I the one paying for them?
我们需要你 维克多
We need you, Victor.
也许你也需要我们
And maybe you need us.
我觉得我一个人就挺好
I'll be fine alone.
很久以前我也是这么对自己说的
I told myself the same for a long time.
我曾经失去了我最爱的人
I lost someone I loved once.
我把自己封闭起来…谁也不见
I shut myself off from... From everyone.
但我必须学会重新敞开心扉
But I had to learn to open back up again.
事实上 我现在还在努力
The truth is I'm still working on it.
既然你同意见我
And if you agreed to meet me...
意味着你也同样在努力
...you're working on it, too.
相信我 维克多
Trust me, Victor.
求救 求救
Mayday! Mayday!
有东西从空中飞下来了
Something came down from the sky.
快救救我
Please, help me!
威士忌
Whisky.
给他也倒一杯
And one for Ahab there.
从空中而来
...from the sky...
我听到一声巨响
I heard a cannon.
- 那不过是大海的怒吼 - 他们来了
- It's ocean's rage. - Then they came...
从天上来的
Monsters.
怪物
...from the sky.
撕碎了我的船
Tore right through my boat.
怪物
Monsters...
记他账上
It's on him.
你撞得不轻
You took a hell of a hit.
你还好吧？
You all right?
终于…
At last...
亚特兰蒂斯女王心爱的长子出现了
The firstborn of beloved Queen Atlanna.
等等
Wait.
拜托了
Please.
我认识她
I knew her.
可我不认识
That makes one of us.
当我的父母在战争中战死
When my parents fought in the wars...
- 她收留了我 - 真是个圣人
- She took me in. - What a saint.
你胆敢这么说亚特兰娜女王？
You dare speak of Queen Atlanna that way?
你的女王把我扔在了我父亲的家门口
Your Queen left me on my father's doorstep
然后再也没想过我
and never gave me another thought...
你母亲那么做是为了救你
Your mother left you to save your life.
你不知道她有多伤心
You can't imagine how it hurt her.
她付出了什么
What it cost her.
但你现在不是一个无助的孩子了
But you're not a defenseless child now.
追着那个怪物到地面
It would've been her responsibility...
并阻止它 本来是她的责任
to follow that monster to the surface and stop it.
现在 是你的了
Now, it's yours.
那我需要你帮我做件事
Then I'm gonna need something from you.
尤里
别弄了，它已经坏了
我明白了 母亲
I see, Mother.
我明白你为什么等到现在才召唤我
I see why you waited to summon me.
氪星人的死让这个怯懦的世界
That Kryptonian's death plunged this timid world...
陷入恐惧
into such terror.
亚马逊人 亚特兰蒂斯人 独自战斗 独自陨落
Amazons. Atlanteans. Each stands, and falls, alone.
我明白 母亲 这一刻你等待得太久了
I know Mother. You've waited too long for the Unity.
我知道 但你会滋养我
I know. But you will feed.
而我的放逐也将结束
And my exile will come to an end.
我会在新神之中找到我的位置
I will take my place among the New Gods.
找到最后一个母盒
Find the last one.
它的力量将会净化这个世界
Its power will cleanse this world.
为了统一之力
For the Unity!
为达克赛德
For Darkseid.
维克多
Victor.
混蛋
Asshole!
八起绑架 六起在大都会 两起在这里
Eight kidnappings. 6 in Metropolis, 2 here.
所有的受害者都是星际实验室的工作人员
All the vics worked for STAR Labs.
被会飞的吸血鬼攻击
Attacked by a flying vampire.
嫌犯是长着大獠牙的
Suspect was a giant bat...
巨型蝙蝠
with huge fangs.
受害者中有一个小孩 吓坏了
One of them was a little kid, scared.
什么都没说只画了这个
Won't say a word but drew this.
- 这看起来… - 我知道这看起来像什么
- Looks like... - I know what it looks like.
拜托 他在哥谭市打击罪犯二十年了
Come on. You think he fights criminals for 20 years here...
你觉得他会去大都会绑架八个人？
and then he goes to Metropolis and kidnaps eight people?
我今晚和他谈谈
I'll talk to him tonight.
整个世界都疯了 吉姆 也许他也疯了
The world's gone crazy, Jim. Maybe he did, too.
你找到钢骨了吗？
You find the Cyborg?
我们谈了谈
We spoke.
给他点时间
Give him time.
你一定是巴里了 我是戴安娜
You must be Barry. I'm Diana.
你好巴里 我是戴安娜
Hi Barry, I'm Diana...
说反了 抱歉
That's not right. Great.
就我们几个了
So this is us?
是啊 就我们几个
Yeah. This is us.
厉害
Oh! Awesome!
那个是蝙蝠标记 那是你的…
That's the Bat-signal. That's your...
抱歉
Oh. Sorry.
那是给你的信号 看来我们得出发了
That's your signal. That means we have to go now.
- 没错 就是这个意思 - 太酷了
- Yeah. That's what that means. - That's so cool.
你们有多少人
How many of you are there?
没多少
Not enough.
八个人在星际实验室附近被绑架了
Eight people abducted from or near STAR Labs.
这个是嫌疑人
Here's the potential perp.
类魔
Parademons.
好吧
Okay...
这些类魔一定闻到了母盒的气味
The demons must have caught the scent of a Mother Box.
它们把人抓走 看看他们知道什么
They carried people away to find out what they know.
- 那这八个人可能还活着 - 九个
- So the eight might still be alive. - Nine.
星际实验室的负责人也被抓走了
The head of STAR Labs was taken as well.
你想通了
You made it.
那么 附近一定有个巢穴
So then. There must be a nest nearby.
我标注了大都会 哥谭市所有的目击地点
I plotted all the sightings in Metropolis, Gotham...
看不出来什么花样
No pattern I can see.
地图上的线并不交汇
The lines on the map don't converge.
陆地上
On land.
这些线都指向两座城市之间的布拉克斯顿岛
These lead back to Braxton Island, between the two cities.
哥谭港口 这些是排气塔
Gotham Harbor. These are air vents...
它们都通向大都会的地道
they all lead down to the tunnel from Metropolis...
这个项目1929年就废弃了
project that was abandoned in '29.
你真的认为…
Do you really think that...
他们就… 他们就这么消失了
Wow. They just... They really just vanished.
好没礼貌
That's rude.
- 阿尔弗雷德 到哪儿了？- 布拉克斯顿岛
- Where are we, Alfred? - Braxton Island.
你们应该在…
You should be...
隧道排气塔的正下方
directly under the venting tower for the tunnel.
现在看你们的左边 应该有一段楼梯
Now, look to your left, you should see a staircase.
爬上去就可以直接进入机房
It will give you access to the machine room.
果然够直接
Define access.
一个一个过
One at a time.
这桥可能…
The bridge may not...
撑不住
...hold.
把实话告诉我就行
Just tell me the truth.
求你了 放我们走吧
Please, just let us go.
- 我还有家人 - 回答错误
- I have a family! - Wrong answer.
人类…
Humans...
你们恐惧的气味让我的士兵垂涎欲滴
The stench of your fear is making my soldiers hungry.
我该喂它们吗？
Shall I feed them?
你靠近过母盒
You've been near the Mother Box.
- 你身上有它的气味 - 求你了
- The scent is on you... - Please.
我们都有家人
We have families.
为什么每个人都告诉我这个
Why does everyone keep telling me that?
事情是这样的
Okay. Here's the thing...
瞧 我害怕虫子 还有…
See, I'm afraid of bugs, and...
枪 还有个子高的人
Guns. And obnoxiously tall people.
还有谋杀 我待不下去了
And murder. I can't be here.
你们已经准备好去战斗了 这挺棒的
It's really cool, you guys seem ready to do battle and stuff, but...
但说实话 我从来没有战斗过
Full transparency, I've never done battle.
我以前都是推别人一下就跑
I just push some people and run away.
救一个
Save one.
一个？
One?
救一个人
Save one person.
哪一个？
Wait, which one?
别说话 别打架 进去 救一个出来
Don't talk. Don't fight. Get in. Get one out.
然后呢？
And then?
你会明白的
You'll know.
好吧
Okay.
真没用
Useless!
到你了
You then.
我的母盒在哪里？
Where is my Mother Box?
我死也不会告诉你
I'll die before I tell you.
终于找到一个有骨气的人了
At last, one that doesn't whine.
但我会让你尖叫的
But you will scream.
爸爸
Dad.
维克多
Victor.
你是母盒孕育的
You were born of her.
一个混沌的生物
A creature of chaos.
我可不这样想
Not how I see it.
不着急
Give it time.
亚马逊人
Amazon!
好吧
Okay.
救一个
Save one.
这个是我的
This one is mine.
你太高估自己了
You overestimate yourself.
孩子…
Child...
我的斧子上还滴着你姐妹的血呢
My axe is still slick with the blood of your sisters.
阿尔弗雷德 我需要"夜行者"
Alfred, I need the Nightcrawler.
还以为你不需要呢
I thought you'd never ask.
夜行者已出发 开启远程操纵模式
Crawler's on the way. Initiating remote mode.
你没事吧
You good?
大厅的尽头应该有个楼梯
At the end of the hall there should be stairs.
好的
Okay.
快走
Go!
他在找再造引擎 是他的母盒
He's after the change engine. His Mother Box.
- 你不能让他接近它 - 带他们去安全的地方
- You have to keep him from it. - Help people get to safety.
- 答应我 - 快走
- Promise me. - Go!
杀了她
Finish her!
抱歉 各位
Sorry guys,
我没带剑来
I didn't bring a sword.
天啊 他真高
Jesus. He is tall.
原来…
So...
你体内流淌着旧神的血液
You have the blood of the Old Gods in you.
旧神已经灭亡了
The Old Gods died.
不
No!
小心
Heads up!
谢了 阿尔弗雷德 不过后面的事交给我吧
Thanks, Alfred. But I'll take it from here.
我认识你吗？
Do I know you?
一群原始人类
Primitive beings.
我们上面是什么？
What are we under right now?
哥谭港口
Gotham Harbor.
你们最好躲开点
You all need to move.
- 你带他出去 - 戴安娜 没有时间了
- You get him out... - Diana, there's no time.
而且溺水也是我恐惧的
Also among my fears is drowning.
你们真让人分心
You are a distraction.
母亲在召唤我
Mother is calling.
戴安娜 快走
Diana, come on!
拜托
Come on.
再造引擎
The change engine.
他就这么逃了吗？
Did he just bail?
数百万美元的工程毁了
Millions in structural damage.
你手段依旧啊
You haven't lost your touch.
但是很高兴能看到你和别人相处得这么好
But it's good to see you playing well with others.
穿得像个蝙蝠吗？我喜欢
Dressed like a bat? I dig it.
也许只是暂时的
It may be temporary.
那么…
So...
是什么让你改变主意了？
What made you change your mind?
荒原狼
Steppenwolf.
是他夺走了亚特兰蒂斯族的母盒
He took the Mother Box from Atlantis.
他现在只需要人类手里的最后一个盒子了
All he needs now is the last box of man.
如果他还没有得到的话
If he doesn't already have it.
他还没有拿到
He doesn't have it.
我们得走了
不  我们在这里很安全
食物吃完了怎么办？
会有人来的
谁会来救我们
这里就像一个洞穴
It's like a cave.
像个蝙蝠洞
Like a Batcave.
巴里
Barry!
我父亲叫它再造引擎
My father called it the change engine.
这是英国人在一战期间发现的
It was found by the British during World War I.
他们研究了它
They studied it...
但是他们看不出制作的年代 它太古老了
but they couldn't even date it. It's so old.
它被搁置一边 直到超人去世的那晚
It was shelved, until the night Superman died.
它就像圣诞节的彩灯一样亮了起来
Then she lit up like Christmas.
他们把它带到星际实验室
They brought it to STAR Labs...
我父亲认出
where my father recognized it...
这是一个永恒的能量矩阵
as a perpetual energy matrix.
听起来很酷
That sounds cool.
我还以为这是个核弹呢
I thought it was like a nuclear bomb.
母盒既能毁灭也能创造
A Mother Box destroys as it creates.
它是生命的循环 但是快了一百万倍
It's a cycle of life, but a million times faster.
我父亲认为它是能量无限化的关键
My father thought it was the key to unlimited energy.
新的公式 细胞再生…
New formulas, cellular regeneration...
但它很不稳定 难以控制
But it's too volatile to control.
他拿你做实验了
He used it on you.
我出了场事故
I was in an accident.
我本来会死的
I should've died.
我父亲觉得 他可以利用母盒
My father thought that he could use the Mother Box to
用改装机械来重建我受损的身体部位
rebuild the broken parts of me with a few cybernetic enhancements.
但是 他造出的是个活的机器
Instead, he built a living machine.
可能比宿主还要强大
It may be stronger than its host.
太多了 活性元素过多了
Too much. Too much life.
你脑袋里在想什么？
What's on your weird mind?
肌肉 协调性
Muscles. Coordination.
细胞的基本完整性
Basic cellular integrity.
人类只能接受得了这么多
A human being can only absorb so much.
母盒本来是被用于重建一个星球的
The Mother Box was designed to reshape a planet.
所以？
So?
所以…
So...
如果你比一个星球还要强大呢
What if you were stronger than a planet?
你的细胞处于休眠状态 但是不会腐烂
Your cells lying dormant, but incapable of decay.
如果让你处于一个导电领域…
If you were in a conductive field...
借用母盒上的能量…
A boost from the Mother Box...
可以让他起死回生
could bring "him" back to life.
氪星飞船上有一个羊膜舱
The Kryptonian ship has an amniotic chamber...
- 那是个完美的… - 不
- Which would be a perfect... - No.
- 戴安娜 - 布鲁斯 不行
- Diana. - Bruce, no!
你根本不知道你面对的是何种能量
You have no idea what kind of power you're dealing with.
即使只有一点机会…
Even if there was a fraction of a chance...
那又怎样？我们要养一个怪物吗？
That what? That we could raise a monster?
像卢瑟那样？
Like Luthor did?
我们有卢瑟没有的科技…
We have tech Luthor's never even seen...
超人已经死了
Superman is dead.
虽然我们都希望他没死
We all wish he weren't.
我们不知道他现在处于什么状态
We don't know what state he's in.
我知道我们没法带他回来
We know we can't bring him back.
但是这有超越我们极限的科技
But this is science beyond our limits.
这正是科技的作用
And that's what science is for.
做从没做过的事 让生命更美好
To do what's never been done. To make life better
或者毁灭生命
Or to end it.
科技像其他力量一样
Technology is like any other power...
没有理性 没有心灵的话 它会毁灭我们
Without reason, without heart... It destroys us.
你在冒险
You're risking lives.
拿他们的和无数其他人的生命冒险
Theirs and maybe countless more.
我们没时间慢慢研究了
We don't have time for a control group.
有风险吗 是的 但是必须这么做
Is it a risk? Yes. But it's necessary.
为什么 因为你的内疚吗
Why? Because of your guilt?
布鲁斯 我当时在那
Bruce, I was there.
你没有害死超人
You didn't kill Superman.
有时候 即使是你…也得学会往前看
At some point, even you... have to learn to move on.
史蒂夫·特雷弗教你的吧？
Did Steve Trevor tell you that?
超人 曾是这个世界的指路灯
Superman, was a beacon to the world.
为什么你不是？
Why aren't you?
你可以激励人 戴安娜
You're an inspiration, Diana.
你不只是救人
You don't just save people.
你让他们发现自己更美好的一面
You make them see their better selves.
可是 我从没听说过你…
And yet, I never heard of you...
直到卢瑟偷走了
Until Luthor lured you out
你死去的男朋友的照片 才引出了你
by stealing a picture of your dead boyfriend.
你自我封闭了一个世纪
You shut yourself down for a century.
所以别跟我谈什么向前看
So let's not talk about me moving on.
你知道…
You know...
如果她杀了你 我们替她打掩护的
That if she kills you, we'll cover for her.
我们的力量不够
We are not enough.
我们每个人都有自己的弱点
Each of us in our own way has held back.
我可以保证 荒原狼不会管什么伦理道德
And I promise you, Steppenwolf is not out there talking about ethics.
他想要毁灭整个世界
He's trying to burn down the world.
我们能阻止他的办法…
The way we're gonna stop him...
就是利用它的能量
is by using his power.
这份力量
This power,
来对抗他
against him.
我同意
I agree.
我可不想看到母盒重新合并
I don't like the idea of reintegrating with the Mother Box...
但是我在你犯浑的时候运算了成功率
But I was running the numbers while you're being an asshole,
我们成功复活他的几率很高
and there's a high probability that we can bring him back.
好 但他复活的场景最好像…
Right, but we mean bring him back, in like a...
太好啦 他复活啦 而不是…
"Yay! He's back!" way. Not in like a...
像《宠物坟场》
Like a Pet Sematary
那样
scenario?
死忘的时候都会失去些东西 超人也不例外
You lose something when you die. Even Superman.
也许不是他的理智 而是他的灵魂
Maybe not his mind. Maybe his soul.
我会想个应急方案的
I'll have a contingency plan for that.
如果他醒来第一眼看到的就是你…
If he wakes up and you're the first thing he sees...
你确实需要应急方案
You'll need one.
这真有趣 虽然没有继续下去
Well that was fun while it didn't last.
她可以阻止我的 我实际上是在激她
She could've stopped me. I practically dared her to.
我不明白你为什么要一直逼她
I don't see why you're pushing her.
我们需要增强信号
We'll have to boost the signal.
通过蝙蝠车的音响放出来
Put it through the Batmobile's speakers.
你又转移话题
Now you're changing the subject.
- 我有应急方案 - 什么
- I have a contingency. - What?
戴安娜说的是对的
Diana was right about the risk.
如果这个计划行不通 我们就得拿出大家伙了
If the plan goes south, we're gonna bring in the big guns.
但 那可是…
But that's not...
非同小可的大家伙
Those are very big guns.
你在这里有一个团队了
You got a team here.
带领这个团队 超人会比我更出色
Superman could bring this team together better than I ever could.
- 他的力量… - 这无关强壮与力量
- His strength... - It doesn't matter how strong you are.
或者你所拥有的超能力
Or what abilities you might have.
他比我更有人性
He was more human than I am.
他在这个世界生活过
He lived in this world.
爱过某人 有过工作
Fell in love, had a job.
就算抛开那些超能力不谈
In spite of all that power.
世界也需要超人
The world needs Superman.
这个团队也需要克拉克
And the team needs Clark.
那克拉克需要什么呢？
And what does Clark need?
也许他已经安息了
Maybe he's at peace.
他会没事的
He'll get over it.
(拉克·约瑟夫·肯特)
你知道吗 我其实可以很快挖完的 只是…
You know, I can do this a lot faster. I just...
我感觉这样有点不敬 是不是有点奇怪？
Is it weird that it feels disrespectful?
是的
Yep.
你有没有觉得…
Do you feel a sense of confidence
我们在做一件极其错误的
that we're not doing something horribly wrong
恐怖的事
and macabre here?
没有
Not really.
- 好吧那为什么… - 因为我看到过荒原狼
- Okay then why are... - Because I saw Steppenwolf up close.
戴安娜告我们的故事
The stories Diana told us?
我相信是真的
And I believe them.
但是我们会阻止他的
But we're gonna stop him.
计划是这样的
That's the plan.
That's the plan!
好吧 我们还没有到… 跨越种族那一步
Okay, we're not ready for... Racially charged...
你是被闪电击中了 对吗？
You got struck by lightning, huh?
对 长话短说 是的
Yeah... That's the abridged version.
- 那你… - 爆炸
- And you... - Explosion.
在一间实验室醒来
Woke up in a lab.
我们都是意外的结果
We're, we're the accidents.
是 我们都是意外
Yeah, that's us.
来碰一个吧 不要吗
Hey! No. No.
我们正在接近氪星飞船
We're approaching the Kryptonian ship.
预计30秒后到达
ETA, 30 seconds.
我是为他来的
I'm here for him.
- 我发誓 我永远不会… - 省省吧
- I swear, I would never... - Save it.
(星际实验室个人档案 韦斯利·罗 军警)
- 好了 - 好的
- Okay. - Okay!
好了
Okay.
这太棒了
This is amazing.
这太疯狂了
This is crazy.
你现在才觉得疯狂吗？
What, now it's crazy?
你们这帮疯子最好知道自己在干吗
You lunatics better know what you're doing.
莱克斯·卢瑟烧毁了电路 才让他的怪物活过来
Lex Luthor fried the circuits bringing his creature to life.
现在的电压不足以唤醒盒子
There's not enough charge to wake the Box.
我也许能做到
I might be able to do it.
我也许可以启动它
I might be able to jumpstart it, I...
如果我有足够远的距离
If I can get enough distance...
我可以制造一个足够强大的电流
I can conduct a significant electrical current.
也许可以唤醒盒子
I might be able to wake the Box,
如果 确定要这样的话
if that's still what we want?
我们必须得试试
We have to try.
这就是最远了 所以…
This must be the end of the line, so...
我就位了
I'm in position.
母盒已经准备好
The Mother Box is ready.
你必须在它接触液体的那一瞬间 把电导进去
You have to charge it the moment it touches the fluid.
五
Five.
戴安娜说得对 这不是个好主意
Diana's right. This is a bad idea.
四
Four.
三
Three.
Three...
二
Two.
一
One.
请求支援…
Give us an ETA on all additional units...
他复活了
He's back.
他不太对劲
He's not all right.
他在扫描我们
He's scanning us.
什么
What?
亚瑟 你放松 你的肾上腺素现在狂飙
Arthur, you need to relax. Your adrenaline's spiking.
因为他不太对劲
Because he's not all right.
完了
Oh, no.
我们要不要鞠躬？或者是把肚子露给他
Should we bow? Or show our bellies?
维克多
Victor...
维克多 停下来
Victor, stop.
- 糟糕 - 你在干嘛
- Shit! - What are you doing?
维克多
Victor.
- 这是我盔甲的防御机制 - 不要
- It's my armor's defense system... - No.
检测到他就增强了
It's stronger since the interface...
- 我控制不了它 - 维克多 不要
- I can't control it. - Victor, no!
- 把它关掉 - 想想开心的事 维克多
- Shut it off! - Think of happy thoughts, Victor!
凯·艾尔 不要
Kal-El, no!
他不清醒 他不知道自己是谁
He's confused, he doesn't know who he is.
这下成《宠物公墓》了
Pet Sematary.
亚瑟 我们得控制住他
Arthur, we need to restrain him.
我来
I got him.
凯·艾尔 氪星最后的儿子
Kal-El, the last son of Krypton...
记住你是谁
Remember who you are.
告诉我你是…
Tell me who you...
克拉克
Clark...
我认识你
I know you.
拜托 请别逼我这么做
Please don't make me do this.
阿尔弗雷德 我需要大家伙
Alfred, I need the big gun...
- 是你干的 - 我必须如此
- You did this... - I had to.
你不让我活
You won't let me live.
也不让我死
You won't let me die.
世界需要你
The world needs you.
但它需要你吗？
But does it need you?
告诉我…
Tell me...
你也会流血吗？
Do you bleed?
克拉克
Clark.
别这样
Please...
求求你
Please.
不要这样
Please,
走吧
just go.
好吗？
Yeah?
我们走吧
Let's go. Yeah...
天啊 我肯定哪里流血了
Yeah. Something's definitely bleeding.
母盒
The Mother Box.
他拿到最后一个了
He has the last one.
你把我们带到这里来了
You brought us here.
你还记得
You remembered.
这是我们的家
This is home.
你真好闻
You smell good.
我以前不好闻吗？
Did I not before?
别这样
Don't do that.
我们刚刚被痛扁了一顿
We just got our asses handed to us
荒原狼拿到了第三个盒子
and Steppenwolf has got the third Box.
我们会找回来的
So we find them.
如果这些盒子彼此靠近一些
If the Boxes are even close to each other
肯定会有某种
there's going to be some kind
能量激增
of energy surge.
荒原狼肯定会把它们藏到难以探测的地方
And Steppenwolf's gonna be keeping them somewhere where they don't read.
没有网络 没有卫星信号覆盖的区域
No internet, no satellite coverage.
那范围可是缩小了
That narrows it down.
还不够小
Not enough.
就看 是你找不到呢…
See, you can't find them...
还是你根本不想找
...or maybe you don't want to.
亚瑟
Arthur.
这可真是摆脱超人的好办法
Yeah, that was a great way to get rid of Superman.
哥们 我不是故意的
Man, I'm not doing this on purpose.
对 因为你控制不了你身上的机器
Right. Because you can't control the machine.
我现在提一下我低血糖的事情
Right, so is this a bad time
是不是不太好
to bring up my blood sugar?
我真的好饿
Very hungry...
维克多
Victor...
你能找到那些盒子的
You can find the Boxes.
你跟他们共享能量
You share their energy.
我知道这很吓人 但是如果你出事了
I know it's frightening. But if you go under...
我发誓 我们会救你的
I promise, we will pull you back out.
我干活儿的时候让那个美人鱼离我远点就行
Just keep the Little Merman away from me while I work.
巴里 去找阿尔弗雷德吃点东西
Barry, go find Alfred in the pantry.
然后回来就连线
Then come back, get online.
大家互相核对一下进展
Everybody check everybody else's work.
听着
Listen,
我想知道 你能不能
just wonder if you could, put out a,
就是 你不是水生的嘛
if you were, an aquatic...
你懂的…
You know...
你能不能 跟鱼说话
Do you, talk to fish?
是水在跟鱼说话
The water does the talking.
当然了
Of course.
如果水流有什么异常 我都会知道的
If the current comes in strange, I'm gonna point the way.
好的
Okay.
等等
Wait.
我来吧
Let me.
只是有点脱臼
Isn't this a little out of place.
克拉克的反应跟你料想的一样
So, Clark seemed to share your view on being woken up.
他差点就杀了你
He could've killed you.
他能回来 我受点罪也值得
I was willing to make the trade.
还把露易丝带过来了？
And bringing in Lois Lane?
在机库里 你跟我说良知的那些话 你还记得吗？
Remember what you told me about heart, in the hangar?
你肯定…
I bet you...
认为我没听进去
thought I wasn't listening.
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道自己不可能永远当蝙蝠侠的
You know you can't do this forever.
我现在都已经很勉强了
I can barely do it now.
荒原狼来了…
Steppenwolf...
这是我的职责
This is the job.
是我的职责
It's my job.
一直以来 我都没尽过职
And I haven't been doing it.
一直在被动应对
I've been reacting.
不是主动出击
Not leading.
你说的那些关于史蒂夫·特雷弗的话…
You know, what you said about Steve Trevor...
我不该提起那些事情 抱歉了
That wasn't my business. I'm sorry.
你是想用激将法让我来领导团队
You were pushing me to lead the team.
但是决策失误的话会死人的
But leaders get people killed.
战斗时
I fought...
我从来…
Always...
都不会退缩
When I was needed.
但要去领导团队 走到大家面前…
But to lead, to step into the light...
告诉他们
And to say to people:
这值得去牺牲自己的生命
"This is worth your life?"
要是我搞砸了的话…
When it's your fault...
大家就都成了史蒂夫·特雷弗
They're all Steve Trevor.
我们只要撑过今晚
We make it through tonight...
以后你就可以永远待在黑暗中
You can stay in the shadows forever.
打扮成蝙蝠的样子
Dressed up like a bat.
我不会告你侵权的
I won't even sue.
前提是…我们能撑过今晚
If... we get through the night.
你还好吧
Are you okay?
你把我们带到这里来 可你几乎没在家里待过一分钟
You brought us here, but you've hardly spent a minute in the house.
我知道 我…
I know... I...
我只是需要缓一缓
Just got out of a wooden box.
重新回来这个世界
What was it like...
感觉怎么样
Coming back?
很痒
Itchy.
我 老实说…
I mean, honestly...
感觉怪怪的
Weird,
很多地方都很怪
in so many ways.
- 但主要的是… - 我不够坚强
- But, mostly just - I wasn't strong.
我没能…
I didn't...
你一定对我很失望
You would've been very disappointed in me.
我没有…
I wasn't...
我还是露易丝·莲恩 一个尽责的记者
Lois Lane, dedicated reporter. I...
我真的…
I just...
没关系
It's okay.
我像个白痴一样 离开了你
I'm the idiot who left.
但是我回来了
But I'm back now...
我会让一切重回正轨
And I'm gonna make things right.
你把妈妈也叫过来了？
You called mom?
当然了
Of course.
谢谢
Thank you.
我还以为你需要更长时间来…
I was hoping it was gonna take you longer to...
恢复
...recover.
为什么？
Why?
因为现在我必须送你走了
Because now, I have to send you away.
布鲁斯
Bruce.
他需要你
He needs you.
拯救这个世界的命运 我还以为你们都商量好了 他还…
Fate of the world. I think that's the deal. He was...
挺紧张的
Pretty tense.
看来我确实还欠他一命
Well, I guess I do owe him one.
是啊
Right.
这次不准死了
But no dying.
独家新闻要留给我
And I get the exclusive.
遵命
Yes, madam.
- 真的是你吗 - 真的是我 妈妈
- You're really you? - I'm really me, ma.
终于齐了
At last.
统一之力万岁
Praise to the Unity.
合并吧
The three is one.
恐惧之母万岁
Praise to the Mother of Horrors.
荒原狼在那里吗？
Is Steppenwolf there?
抱歉
Sorry.
在波扎尔诺夫 俄罗斯北部地区
It's Porzenov. In Northern Russia.
是个核电站
The Nuclear Plant.
30年前发生了一次事故
Had a meltdown 30 years ago.
还是有些人想搬回去定居
There have been some attempts to resettle nearby...
但是那里看起来十分的荒凉
but it looks like really rough sledding.
谁愿意去这种地方扎根
Who picks this place to put down roots?
那些被全世界抛弃的人
People that are making it count everywhere else.
地球将发生变化…
The Earth starts changing...
会从那里开始
it'll hit them first.
我们还剩多少时间
How long have we got?
几个小时吧
A few hours.
普通的交通工具可飞不到那里
Transport won't fly that fast.
交给我吧
It will for me.
统一之力让三个母盒精确同步
The Unity brings all three boxes together in perfect sync.
它的能量不断汇聚 直到溢出来
Its power builds until it can't be contained.
但我们要是能让每个盒子之间有一点延迟
But if I can cause a delay between each box,
哪怕延迟一纳秒
even for a nanosecond...
它的能量就会泻出形成一个闭环
Its energy will cascade. Form a loop.
然后它们之间就会互相侵蚀
And they'll feed on each other.
就这么简单吗？直接分开就行了吗？
And that's it? We just pull them apart?
没什么可怕的后果吗？
No fuss, no muss?
分开母盒的时候还是会引发大规模的能量振荡
Separating the boxes is still gonna cause a massive surge.
我必须在那里
I have to be there.
但你们得快点想办法撤离
But you guys should think about getting clear.
我们是不会丢下你的
We're with you 'till it's done.
说实话
Honestly...
恐怕还没到那个时候我们就全死了
I think we're gonna be dead way before that.
你们知道吗？
And you know what?
我倒不介意 这是个光荣的死法
I don't mind. It's an honorable end.
但我们必须阻止荒原狼
But we've gotta shut Steppenwolf down.
超人是不会来了
Superman's a no-show.
你又没有超能力
You've got no powers.
无意冒犯
No offense.
这家伙也可能是个内鬼 谁知道呢
This guy might be working for the enemy. We don't know.
而你经常绊倒自己
You're tripping over your feet, and mine...
你太动人了
You're gorgeous.
也很勇猛
And fierce...
很强壮
And strong. And...
我知道我的族人曾经和亚马逊族交战过 但…
I know we went to war with the Amazons, but...
不过那时候还没有我
but that was before my time.
你们猜怎么着？我不想死
You know what? I don't wanna die.
我很年轻 我也还没活够呢
I'm young. There's shit that I wanna do.
我只是觉得…
I just feel like...
我还没有真正的拥抱过海洋和陆地
I didn't really embrace the sea or the land.
到现在我还是孤身一人
I've been a loner my whole life.
能成为伟大行动的一部分
But being part of something bigger,
就像这样
like this...
也许我害怕是因为…
Maybe I'm scared because...
我注定要…
I'm meant to...
我觉得你的发言很精彩
I think that was beautiful.
你要是还敢提这件事 我就把你扔到海里喂鱼
You say a word about this, and I'll meet every prawn I know.
他说到我们都会死之后 我就什么都没听到了
I honestly didn't hear anything after "We're all gonna die."
让他们来吧
Let them come.
我会拆了那座塔 来突破防护罩
I'm gonna take out that tower and knock down that shield dome.
你们去阻止荒原狼
You get to Steppenwolf.
不用等我 完成任务就行了
Don't wait for me. Just do the job.
好了 阿尔弗雷德 准备开始广播
Alright, Alfred. Are we set to broadcast?
马上播放你最爱的金曲
Playing all your favorite hits.
来啊 追我啊 臭虫们
Come on, follow me, you damn insects.
他们来了
They're coming.
他们全来了
They're all coming.
我们好像没考虑到这种情况
We might not have thought this through.
他在吸引火力
He's clearing the field.
他顶不过三分钟的
He won't last three minutes.
那我们就好好利用这三分钟
Then let's use them.
听我指挥
On my lead.
他们飞走了
爸爸
走  我们出去
妈的一群害虫
Son of a bitch.
不用谢
You're welcome.
计划可不是这样的
This isn't the plan.
确实不是 韦恩少爷
No, Master Wayne...
这就是团队
this is the team.
要怪就怪女侠吧
Hey, blame the lady.
我们是想扔下你的
We would've left you
但是她都没要我们投票
but she didn't ask for our vote.
所以你的天才计划 就是送死？
So your genius move is dying?
你可真是疯了
You really are out of your mind.
拿鱼叉打仗的人才叫疯了
I'm not the one who brought a pitchfork.
- 事情还没结束呢 - 这才像话
- Ride aingt over yet. - My man.
征服就是这个样子吗？
Is this what conquering is?
连干一架都不敢
Hiding from the fight?
不…
Oh, no...
你们都归我了
You're all mine.
- 谢谢让我搭便车 - 没事
- Thanks for the lift. - Yeah, no problem.
你能搞定吗？
You got this?
这些家伙不停的来
These things are gonna keep coming.
你搞技术活 我来除虫吧
You get technical. I'm on bug duty.
开始吧
Let's do it.
对 好恶心
Yes! That's gross.
谢谢你
Thank you.
这可不是…
This is not...
现在 你明白了吗？
Now,do you see it?
不管你周围是什么
Whatever you're in the middle of...
它都蔓延好几英里了
It's spreading for miles.
卫星显示有平民在向东逃跑
Satellites show civilians moving east.
他们可能逃不出去了
They're not gonna make it.
巴里
Barry...
我需要你跑一趟
I need you to take a walk.
天哪 希望这是东边
God, I hope this is east.
戴安娜
Diana.
你没资格触碰 母亲…
You're not worthy, to touch. Mother.
她就是力量
She's power.
而力量
And power,
就是唯一的法则
is the only law.
你们太渺小 看不到真理
They're all too weak to see the truth.
是吗
Well...
我相信真理
I believe in truth.
但我刚好也喜欢正义
But I'm also a big fan of justice.
好了
All right!
氪星人
Kryptonian.
那 我能帮上什么忙
So. How do I help?
我们给他争取时间
We buy him some time,
他就可以阻止母盒毁灭整个地球
he can stop that box from destroying all life on Earth.
希望如此
We hope.
好吧 我知道你复活我 不是因为爱上我了
Well, I knew you didn't bring me back because you like me.
我不…不是…
I don't... not...
平民
Civilians...
- 巴里去了 - 人太多了
- Barry is headed... - There's too many of them.
对 这绝对是东面
Oh, yeah. This is definitely east.
小乌龟
Slowpoke.
要比赛是吧
Oh, it's on.
右边的归我
I'll take the ones on the right.
没事的
It's okay.
抓好 抓好
Hold on. Hold on.
陀思妥耶夫斯基
Dostoyevski!
这家伙还在烦你吗？
Is this guy still bothering you?
超人
Superman!
我们得把这些东西分开
We gotta pull these things apart.
再等几秒
A couple of more seconds...
你就会看到机会
you'll see her opening.
会有冲击波吗？
Any blow-back?
很强
Big-time.
但是我觉得我们承受的住
But I think we can take it.
很好
Good...
因为我还是蛮喜欢活着的
Because I really like being alive.
我也是
So do I.
克拉克
Clark.
我收回那句话
I take it back...
我想死
I wanna die.
哥们 我的脚趾好痛
Man, my toes hurt.
我都不明白脚趾疼的物理原理是什么
I don't even understand the physics of how my toes hurt.
小朋友
Children.
我在和一帮小朋友工作
I work with children.
你们看到外面发生的情况了吗？
Have you guys seen what's going on outside?
我是世界的终结者
I am the end of worlds.
你好大胆子
Who are you,
居然敢对抗我
to defy me?
世界…
This world...
将属于我
...is my right!
你永远不会…
You will never...
不
No!
这不可能…
This cannot be...
记得这味道吗？
Recognize that smell?
恐惧
Fear.
不 退下
No! Leave me!
给我滚开
Get off me!
我命令你
I command you!
不
No!
No...
我要杀了你
I'll kill you!
我要把你们全杀了
I'll kill you all!
真棒
Booyah!
还好我没错过这个
Glad I didn't miss this.
我也是
So am I.
对
Yeah.
现在她开心了
Now she's glad.
谢谢你布鲁斯
Thank you, Bruce.
真不知该如何谢谢你
Not enough for what you did.
我犯了个错误
I did a mistake.
弥补而已
That's all.
你怎么从银行把房子赎回来的？
How did you get the house back from the bank?
我把银行买了
I bought the bank.
整个银行？
The whole bank?
跟我说话你得慢一点
Slow your reflex with me.
我老了
I'm old.
什么？
What?
这是犯罪实验室里最糟糕的工作了
It's actually the,worst job you can get in a crime lab.
但…
But, uh...
我迈出了第一步
My foot's in the door.
对 有个朋友推荐的
Yeah. I got a recommendation from a friend.
这是份正经工作吗？
This is like a "job" job?
正经工作
"Job" job.
真不错
Look at you go!
黑暗
Darkness.
真正的黑暗
The truest darkness...
并不是没有光明
...is not the absence of light.
而是深信光明
It is the conviction that the light...
不会重新出现
...will never return.
大概有150英尺
Must be 150 feet.
肯定有
Must be.
大圆桌
Big round table.
六把椅子
Six chairs.
就在那里
Right there.
会有更多位置的
With room for more.
但是光明总会回来
But the light always returns...
带给我们那些熟悉的东西
...to show us things familiar.
家
Home.
家人
Family.
还有完全陌生的
And things entirely new.
或者长期被忽视的东西
Or long overlooked.
让我们看到新的机会
It shows us new possibilities...
鼓励我们去追随
And challenges us to pursue them.
对 杰瑞·摩纳思科是主谋
Yeah. And Johnny Menasco runs the whole thing.
两年前毕尔巴鄂的案子就是他干的
I mean, he did the Bilbao job 2 years ago.
还有克罗伊登的那些储藏箱
As are all the storage in Croydon.
- 那个比利时人 - 对的 就是那个比利时人
- The Belgian. - Right, yeah. The Belgian.
这次 英雄们从黑暗中挺身而出
This time, the light shone on the heroes.
他们的光芒照亮了人世
Coming out of the shadows
告诉我们 我们不再孤单
to tell us we won't be alone again.
当时黑暗那么强大
Our darkness was deep...
仿佛吞噬一切希望
...and seemed to swallow all hope.
但是这些英雄们一直都在
But these heroes were here the whole time.
时刻提醒我们 希望是真实的
To remind us that hope is real.
可以看见的
That you can see it.
你需要做的只是抬头
All you have to do is look...
仰望天空
Up in the sky...
你愿意这么做 我感激不尽
I can't tell you how much I appreciate you doing this.
我不知道 巴里
I don't know, Barry.
我自己也很好奇
I'm curious myself.
对 这可不是比赛 知道吧
Yeah. And it's not like a competition, you know?
好吧 这…
Well, it...
这就是比赛
It is a competition.
但这可不是为了彰显男子气概
But it's not like a macho-measuring thing.
但如果我赢了 你就退出团队
But if I win, you're off the team.
不是啦…
No...
如果我赢了…
If I win...
布鲁斯说 你要请大家去吃早午餐？
Bruce said something about you having to take us all to "brunch"?
瞧 真令人寒心 他背叛了我
Oh, see, now that's cold. That's a betrayal.
我感觉好受伤
I feel stung by that.
好吧 但是如果我赢了 我可以告诉所有人
Okay. But if I win, I get to tell everyone.
一言为定
Deal.
哪个海岸
Which coast?
你知道 我还没见过太平洋呢
You know, I've never seen the pacific.
也就是那边 因为…
Which is that way, because...
太阳 就在…
The sun, and it's...
快来 卢瑟 该走了
Come on, Luthor. Let's go.
卢瑟
Luthor.
好了 别闹了 卢瑟
All right, stop jerking around, Luthor,
别逼我进来逮你
or I'm gonna have to come in there.
你来了 欢迎上船
Ah! There he is. Welcome aboard.
要先来杯香槟吗？
Care for a glass of Goût de Diamants?
我在庆祝超人的回归
I was just celebrating God's return
从地下又飞上了天空
out of the ground and back up into the sky.
他和他那帮怪朋友整出来一个什么联盟
He and his odd little friends are forming some sort of league.
你最好别浪费我的时间
You better not be wasting my time.
当然不 我的事情还多呢 还有更重要的事情要去做
No. I have too much to live for and more important things to do.
我们得让这场竞争公平点 威尔逊先生
We have to level the playing field, Mr. Wilson.
长话短说
To put it plainly
我们是不是也应该组建一个自己联盟呢？
shouldn't we have a league of our own?